http://www.compacc.com/policies

Policies
Updated: September 28,2020.
This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting CompetitionAccessories.com (“CA”, “we” or “us”), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
1. What personal information does CA gather about its customers?
The information we receive from customers helps us personalize and improve your shopping experience at CompetitionAccessories.com (the “Site”). Here are the types of information we gather:
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on the Site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of certain features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as processing orders, assisting your with parts fitment, responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, and communicating with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use “cookies” and we obtain certain types of information when you access the Site.
E-mail Communications: If you make a purchase with us, or if you have otherwise elected to receive e-mails from us, we will not sell your e-mail information. We send you e-mails to confirm orders, provide order status or notifications, for promotional purposes, and to generally to communicate with you. To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from CA. We may also receive information regarding any “click-through” within the e-mail, provided your computer supports such capabilities. If you no longer wish to receive e-mail from us, you are allowed to unsubscribe from promotional emails.
In subscribing for a newsletter you agree that Competition Accessories (700 US 31 East, Clarksville, IN 47129) may use the data you entered to inform you by e-mail about the contents and/or products selected by you. You may revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future, either by written notice to Competition Accessories or by contacting us from our form here. You may also unsubscribe from any newsletter via the link provided at the end of each newsletter or call us at 1-855-518-2281.
2. What about cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as “Your Rides”, fitment data, personalized advertisements, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of CA’s essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any our products and services that require you to Sign in.
3. Does CA share the information it receives?
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below subject to this Privacy Notice.
Third-Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Promotional Offers: Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of CA customers on behalf of other businesses, such as our product manufacturers. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, please unsubscribe from the e-mail list.
Protection of CA and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Site Terms and Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of CA, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
4. How secure is the information about me?
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. We transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
5. What about links to other websites?
The Site may include links to other websites. Once you leave our Site, we no longer have access to or control over cookies, information practices, or other features that third-parties may use. Therefore, third-party websites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.
6. Which information can I access?
CA gives you access to information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
7. What choices do I have?
You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other CA features. You can add or update your account information. When you update information, we may keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please unsubscribe from the e-mail list when you receive an e-mail. (If you do not want to receive Conditions of Use and other legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Notice, those notices will still govern your use of the Site, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.)
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
8. Are children allowed to use CA?
CA does not actively market to children, but does sell some products that are suitable for children, such as toy trucks, stickers, pajamas, etc. If you are under 18, you may use our Site only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.
9. Site Terms and Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit the Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Site Terms and Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the State of Indiana. If you have any concern about privacy at CA, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use may change over time as changes occur in our business and with our Site. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
Follow Us
Newsletter Sign Up
Receive Special Offers,
Tips & Reviews!
©2012-2020 All Rights Reserved.
Site Powered by vNext Technologies, Inc.
Hello
Sign in and enjoy all the member benefits right now.
Sign In
Not a Member Yet?  Start Here
No Thanks, Not Now
